* * Discover 
    * Fundraise for
    * How it Works
    * Resources

For Individuals

Discover 

Fundraise for

How it Works

Resources

Date of Last Revision: January 12, 2024

Privacy Notice
==============

Questions about our privacy notice? [Contact Us](https://support.gofundme.com/hc)

Our Privacy Notice will be updated, and our updated Privacy Notice will be effective starting on September 1, 2024. To view the updated Privacy Notice, [click here](https://www.gofundme.com/c/gofundme-privacy-notice).

Privacy and security are very important to us at GoFundMe. This Privacy Notice (“Notice”) is meant to help you (the “end user”) understand how we at GoFundMe collect, use, and share your data when you use our products or services on which we make this Notice available – for example, when you use GoFundMe or the Classy Platform or our mobile applications, or when you raise funds on GoFundMe for your campaigns or donate to one of our non-profit partners through Classy.Org (collectively, the “Services”). 

This Policy applies to GoFundMe Group Inc. and its affiliates and subsidiaries, including Classy.org, GoFundMe, Inc. and GoFundMe Ireland Ltd (collectively, “GoFundMe” “we,” “our,” and “us”). (Please see the “[Contacting GoFundMe](https://www.gofundme.com/c/privacy#contact)” section below for which of these entities is responsible for processing your data.) You should read this Policy carefully, it contains important information about your privacy rights and choices.

Classy, an affiliate of GoFundMe, is a Public Benefit Corporation and a certified B corporation that helps nonprofit organizations maximize their impact through a suite of online fundraising tools to accelerate social impact around the world. Nonprofits use the Classy platform to raise money, engage their communities, and advance their missions. Classy also hosts the Collaborative conference and the Classy Awards to spotlight the innovative work nonprofits are implementing around the globe.

Before you use or submit any information through or in connection with the Services, please carefully review this Notice. By using any part of the Services, you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information as outlined in this Notice. To the extent allowed by law, the English version of this Notice is binding and its translations in other languages are for convenience only; in case of discrepancies between the English version of this Notice and its translations, the English version shall prevail.

If you are in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), the United Kingdom or Switzerland (collectively “Europe”) and have used the GoFundMe Services under a contractual relationship under the Terms of Service with GoFundMe Ireland, then for the purposes of the EU General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the “GDPR”), the UK GDPR , and the Swiss Federal Act of 19 June 1992 on Data Protection (FADP), the data controller is GoFundMe Ireland Limited. and can be reached at the address set out at [“Contacting GoFundMe”](https://www.gofundme.com/c/privacy#contact) below; and

* For the Users in the EEA that do not fall under the previous paragraph, and to the extent that this would be required by GDPR, GoFundMe Ireland also acts as representative in the EU of GoFundMe Inc.

If you are a resident of California, the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 provides you with additional rights. Please view our “[California Privacy Notice](https://www.gofundme.com/c/ccpa)” to learn more. 

If you are a resident of Colorado, Connecticut, Utah or Virginia, the respective laws in your states provide you with additional rights. Please view our “[Privacy Notice of certain other states in the United States](https://www.gofundme.com/c/privacy-notice-of-certain-other-states-in-the-united-states)” to learn more. 

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**
--------------------------

As further described below, when you use or otherwise access the Services, we collect information in multiple ways, including when you provide information directly to us, and when we passively collect information from your browser or device (e.g., by logging how you interact with our Services).

**A. Information That You Provide Directly to Us:**

**I. Registration information:**When you register for our Services or open an account, we collect registration information, such as your name, email address and login details, your zip code, your country, your phone number (for purposes of multi-factor authentication and to provide you with important messages) and any information you choose to provide us (such as a profile picture). If you are a representative of a Charity (as defined in the Terms) to whom funds are donated through our Services, registration information we collect may include your name and email address.

**II. Creation of a fundraiser:**When you create a fundraiser on the Services, we collect the information you choose to provide us in relation to your fundraiser and we display it through our Services. For example, you can provide a fundraiser title, choose a fundraiser category, upload images, and describe your fundraiser goal(s).      

You might, in creating a fundraiser, choose to provide us with information relating to other parties by organizing a fundraiser for a family member or friend, and in doing so, you disclose the name or circumstances of that family member or friend. By providing information in a fundraiser, you consent to our collection, storage, disclosure, and use of your data.  If you upload personal data related to other parties, you acknowledge and agree that you have the authority and consent of the relevant other parties for us to access, disclose, and use the relevant data and that you have notified the other parties and informed them of how their information is collected and used by GoFundMe to provide the Services. We reserve the right to identify you as the person who has made the referral in any messages that are sent to them.

Our payment processors also collect and maintain information related to your withdrawal of funds from any fundraiser. See more details under “Information collected by our payment processors”. 

**III. Setting up withdrawals:**When you are the beneficiary (or the recipient of funds from a fundraiser), we may collect information including your contact details (such as name and email address), zip code, country, your phone number (for purposes of multi-factor authentication and to send you important messages) and any information you choose to provide us.   

Our payment processors collect your bank details as well as other information necessary to set up the withdrawals. See more details under “Information collected by our payment processors”. 

**IV. Donation information:**On the Services, when you donate to a fundraiser, we may collect information such as your contact details (such as name and email address), physical address for billing purposes, zip code, country, and any information you choose to provide us (such as a description of why you have donated). 

Our payment processors collect your credit card details and other information necessary to process the donation such as your home address. See more details under “Information collected by our payment processors”. 

**V. Public Communications:**You can post comments, leave feedback, send thank-you notes or otherwise communicate with other users through our Services. Any content, including such comments, feedback, and notes that you choose to post on publicly available campaign pages through our Services are available to the public by default. 

Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information for both us and other users to use and share. Take care not to disclose personal data unless you intend for that data to become public. Please also be considerate and respectful of others while using the community to publish your opinions. We reserve the right, but do not have the obligation, to review and monitor such posting or any other content on our Services, and to remove postings or content that may be viewed as inappropriate or offensive to others.

**VI. Communications to GoFundMe:**If you have questions about how GoFundMe handles information about you, you may contact us via a contact form, email, by chat services or by other means (for example, with questions about our Services, for customer support, or to let us know your ideas for new products or modifications to existing products). You may also choose to respond to surveys that we send out or requests for user interviews, or queries about your fundraisers. If you respond to our requests for surveys or interviews, we will collect any information you provide to us and use that information in the manner set forth herein. When you do so, we collect the information you choose to provide us, such as your contact details, any images you choose to upload and the contents and nature of your message.

We may engage vendors to provide certain interactive features on our Services. Your use of these interactive features is voluntary, and we may retain the information that you submit through these features. For example, we may offer an interactive chat feature on the Services for customer service purposes. When you participate in the interactive chat, the contents of the chat may be captured and kept as a transcript. By using these features, you understand that we and our vendors on our behalf may on a real-time basis collect and process the information obtained through the feature. We would ask that you take care not to send financial information or other sensitive personal data to us through our chat services or other means, unless we ask you specifically for that data as part of providing the Services to you.  When you provide such information to us directly, you consent to the processing of this data by GoFundMe and/or our vendors. We collect the information listed in this section for the purposes described below in the sections “Our Use of Information Collected” and “Our Disclosure of Information Collected Through the Services.” 

**VII. Information relating to other parties:**You can choose to provide us with information relating to other parties. For example, if you choose to provide personal information about someone on your fundraiser, you confirm that you have the consent of such person to share their personal information with us. 

**VIII. Sensitive information:**You can also provide us with information about yourself or other parties that are considered sensitive, such as political opinions, race, ethnicity, health information or religious beliefs.  If you post this information in a fundraiser, you choose to provide such information to be published publicly in relation to your fundraiser, donation or otherwise.  Subject to applicable law, GoFundMe may use any information which has manifestly been made public, including processing information about you that reveals sensitive information. 

When you provide such information to us you consent to the processing of this data by GoFundMe and/or its service providers. We collect the information listed in this section for the purposes described below in the sections “Our Use of Information Collected” and “Our Disclosure of Information Collected Through the Services.” 

**IX. Biometric information:**We sometimes collect biometric information through vendors for identity verification, regulatory compliance and fraud prevention purposes. We or vendors we engage may collect a copy of your government-issued ID (i.e., your driver’s license, state ID card, or passport) and a scan of the picture on your valid and unexpired government-issued ID for identification purposes . Our vendors may, with your consent, employ facial recognition technology to verify your identity and share the results of their analysis with us, if needed. GoFundMe does not have access to or otherwise collect or maintain any biometric information.  

Your biometric information will be retained by our vendors, in accordance with applicable retention policies, privacy policies and applicable law.  Please contact us as detailed in the [“Contacting GoFundMe”](https://www.gofundme.com/c/privacy#contact) section to the extent you have any questions regarding your biometric information.

**X. Information Collected by Our Payment Processors**

We use Stripe, Adyen and Paypal for payments, analytics, and other business services. These payment processors may collect personal data including via cookies and similar technologies. The personal data they collect may include transactional data and identifying information about devices that connect to its services. They use this information to operate and improve the services it provides to us, including for fraud detection, loss prevention, authentication, and analytics related to the performance of its services. They operate both as processors for us and independent controllers for the information they collect directly from our users.

You can learn more about Stripe and read its privacy policy at [https://stripe.com/privacy](https://stripe.com/privacy). You can learn more about Adyen and read its privacy policy at [https://www.adyen.com/policies-and-disclaimer/privacy-policy](https://www.adyen.com/policies-and-disclaimer/privacy-policy). You can learn more about Paypal and read its privacy policy at [https://www.paypal.com/us/legalhub/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/us/legalhub/privacy-full)

**XI. Data from Other Parties:**GoFundMe may use vendors to improve the quality of our own user database so that we might improve our Services to you, verification and fraud prevention purposes, and as otherwise described in this Notice.  In addition, GoFundMe obtains contact details and other personal information regarding media contacts and influencers from various groups such as Cision and MuckRack. See the [Cision privacy policy](http://cision.com/us/legal/privacy-policy) and the [Muckrack privacy policy](https://muckrack.com/privacy) for further information.  

**B. Information That is Passively or Automatically Collected:**

**I. Device & Usage Information:**When you interact with GoFundMe through the Services, we automatically receive and store certain information from devices that you use to access the Services. This information is collected passively by using various technologies, and includes the type of geolocation information, Internet browser or mobile device you use, any website from which you have come to the Services, your operating system, and location data through an IP address that identifies the city and state where you logged into the Services . GoFundMe either stores such information itself or such information is included in databases owned and maintained by GoFundMe, and/or its agents or vendors.

**II. Location Information:**When you use the Services to organize a fundraiser, the Services may require that you provide your zip code, city or town, and state or province of residence. Please keep in mind that other users of the Services can view your zip code, city or town, and state or province of residence in connection with the fundraiser. We also use your location information as described in this Notice, such as described above under “Device & Usage Information”, and in an aggregate way, as described below in the “Aggregated Data” section.

**III. Cookies and Other Electronic Technologies:**When you interact with the Services, we try to make that experience simple and meaningful. When you visit our Services, our web server, business providers, and/or the Social Networking Services (defined below) are integrated into the Services, we use cookies or other electronic technologies (such as web beacons or pixel tags) for various purposes. Cookies are small pieces of information that are issued to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website, or access or use a mobile application. That information regarding your use of the Services is stored and sometimes tracked. Web beacons are transparent image files, which enable the Services to track website usage information.  Pixel tags are tiny graphic images with unique identifiers that track online movements of our users. We will refer to the cookies and other technologies identified here collectively as “Cookies” for purposes of this Notice. 

**i. Type of Cookies**Some Cookies are strictly necessary to make our Services available to you (“Essential Cookies”). We cannot provide our Services without these Essential Cookies.  
We also use Cookies for functional purposes in order to maintain and improve our Services or your experiences, and for marketing purposes (collectively, “Non-Essential Cookies”). Some of the Non-Essential Cookies used are set by us to collect and process certain data on our behalf and some are set by third parties and/or our Social Networking Services.  

**Information to and from Social Networking Services**  Non-Essential Cookies include Cookies we use in conjunction with the Social Networking Services. One of the special features of the Services is that it allows you to enable or log into the Services via various social media applications / services, like Facebook or X, or to upload videos using YouTube APIs (“Social Networking Service(s)”). By directly integrating these services, we aim to make your online experiences richer and more personalized. To take advantage of these features, we will ask you to provide your credentials for the applicable Social Networking Service in order to log in to our Services. When you add a Social Networking Services account to the Services or log into the Services using your Social Networking Services account, we will collect relevant information necessary to enable the Services to access that Social Networking Service. As part of such integration, the Social Networking Service will provide us with access to certain information that you have provided to the Social Networking Service (for example, your name and photograph, as well as other information that you permit the Social Networking Service to share with us).

We will use, store, and disclose such information in accordance with this Notice. However, please remember that the manner in which Social Networking Services use, store, and disclose your information is governed by the policies of such third parties, and GoFundMe shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Social Networking Services that may be enabled within the Services. For example, if you upload a video onto your fundraiser using the mobile application for the Services, your video will be uploaded using YouTube and subject to [Google’s Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US) and [Google’s Security Settings](https://myaccount.google.com/permissions?pli=1). You further acknowledge that if you choose to use this feature, your friends, followers, and subscribers on any Social Networking Services you have enabled will be able to view such activity. For example, if you sign on using Meta, Meta’s [privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation) and [terms of service](https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms) would apply to the data Meta might obtain from [your activities](https://www.facebook.com/help/2207256696182627) on GoFundMe. Please visit the terms of use and privacy policy of the relevant Social Networking Service to learn more about your rights and choices, and to exercise your choice about those technologies.  

**ii. Analytics**We use web analytics vendors on our Services, such as those of Google Analytics, to help us analyze how users use the Services, including by noting the website from which you arrive, and providing certain features to you including Google Signal features such as user id tracking, dynamic remarketing, interest-based advertising, audience targeting, behavioral reporting, demographics and interests reporting, user segment analysis, device reporting, display advertising, and video ads reporting. The information collected by the technology will be disclosed to or collected directly by these vendors, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Services. This may result in you seeing advertisements for our Services when you visit other websites. To limit Google Analytics from using your information for analytics, you can install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on by clicking [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). You can also adjust your advertising settings by clicking [here](https://adssettings.google.com/). 

We use vendors to help us understand and analyze how visitors use our services, and to improve the Services. They may collect the following types of information from users of our Services: device IP Address, device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our Services, and details about your use of the Services .

**iii. Why We Use Cookies**We use Cookies to collect information about your access to and use of the Services, including to: (1) allow you to navigate and use all the features provided by our Services; (2) customize elements of the layout and/or content within the Services and remember that you have visited us before; (3) identify the number of unique visitors we receive; (4) improve the Services and learn which functions of the Services are most popular with users; (5) understand how you use the Services (e.g., by learning how long you spend on the Services and where you have come to the Platform from) and (6) marketing our Services to you. As we adopt additional technologies, we may gather additional information through other methods. We will notify you of such changes with updates to this Notice.

**iv. Your Cookie Preferences**Most web and mobile device browsers automatically accept Cookies but, if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that or to notify you each time a cookie is set. 

If you are located in the EU, you will be requested to opt-in to all Cookies other than essential cookies. If you are located in California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah or Virginia, you can learn more about how we use cookies in our “[California Privacy Notice](https://www.gofundme.com/c/ccpa)” or the or the “[Privacy Notice of certain other states in the United States](https://www.gofundme.com/c/privacy-notice-of-certain-other-states-in-the-united-states)”. You can also learn more about Cookies by visiting www.allaboutcookies.org, which includes additional useful information on Cookies and how to block Cookies using different types of browsers or mobile devices.

You can also consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information (e.g., [Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies), [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647), [Mozilla Firefox](http://kb.mozillazine.org/Cookies#Firefox), or [Apple Safari](http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042)).  If you receive tailored advertising on your computer, you can generally control Cookies from being put on your computer by visiting the following:

1. 1. or advertising based in the United States either the [Network Advertising Initiative’s Consumer opt-out](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1) link, the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s Consumer opt-out](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN) link or the [Your Ad Choices for App tool;](http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices) or 
    2. for advertising in Europe, the [Digital Advertising Alliance Consumer Ad Choices opt-out](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) link. 

We do not control any of the above opt-out links and are not responsible for any choices you make using these mechanisms or the continued availability or accuracy of these mechanisms. If your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit these opt-out pages, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, your opt-out may no longer be effective.

If you are accessing our Services through a mobile device, you can also update your privacy settings on your device by setting the “Limit Ad Tracking” and Diagnostics and Usage setting property located in the settings screen of your Apple iPhone or iPad, or by resetting your Android ID through apps that are available in the Play Store. You can also limit information collection by uninstalling the App on your device and you can use the standard uninstall process available as part of your device for this purpose.  Finally, and in connection with the Social Networking Services, you can visit your settings with each of the Social Networking Services to exercise your choice about those technologies. Please note that we do not control these mechanisms maintained by other parties and thus cannot be responsible for their functionality.

**OUR USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**
------------------------------------

GoFundMe uses the information collected from the Services in a manner that is consistent with this Notice. We may use the information that you provide (or otherwise permit the Services to access) for the following purposes:

**A. Communicating With You**We use the information we collect to contact you for administrative purposes (e.g., to provide services and information that you request or to respond to comments and questions). For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the information you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. In addition, we may call you if you are not responding to email and your fundraiser is subject to refunds.

We also use the information we collect to send you communications relating to the Services, such as updates on events, communications relating to products and services offered by us and by third parties, request your feedback on our Services and communications about services we believe will be of interest to you. For example, we can send periodic emails to registered users of the Services relating to their recent interactions with the Services, such as donating to a fundraiser.

**B. Text Messages**:  
You may agree that we can communicate with you regarding your GoFundMe account by SMS, MMS, or text message. When setting up your GoFundMe account, if you click “Send code” by “Text Message,” you agree to receive automated and nonautomated text messages related to your account from or on behalf of GoFundMe at the phone number provided.  You can reply STOP to such text messages to cancel, except for automated text messages related to the security of your account.  Message frequency will vary. Message and data rates may apply. In the event you change or deactivate your mobile telephone number, you agree to promptly update your GoFundMe account information to ensure that your messages are not misdirected. Please note that your wireless service carrier’s standard charges, data rates, and other fees may apply where you access the Services through a mobile device. In addition, downloading, installing, or using certain Services on a mobile device may be prohibited or restricted by your carrier, and not all Services may work with all carriers or devices. 

**C. Providing and Improving the Services**We use the information we collect to operate, maintain, provide and improve our Services such as enabling access to the Platform, customer support, or to complete transactions.  

**D. Security and Fraud Prevention**We use the information we collect to secure our Services and to verify identity, prevent fraud, and to continually improve these aspects of our Services.  This includes our request for your (mobile) telephone number to conduct multi-factor authentication when you create an account and/or at the time you set up withdrawals as a beneficiary.

**E. Analytics, Research and Product Development**We use the information we collect to analyze data usage trends and preferences in order to improve the accuracy, effectiveness, security, usability or popularity of our Services. We may also use the information we collect to train our artificial intelligence/machine learning models. We further use data in connection with our research on our customer demographics, interests, and behavior.

To help our users fundraise more effectively, we employ machine learning and other analytics that make inferences about some characteristics of our users. We use these tools to tailor emails to you, to show and prioritize causes, fundraisers, pages we think you’ll be interested in, and make suggestions about how much you may want to fundraise or donate. 

**F. Customization and Marketing**We may use the information we collect for customization and marketing purposes. For example, we may use device identifiers to learn how users interact with our Services in order to personalize the content of our Services, such as customizing the language and fundraisers on our homepage based on your location.

**G. Legal**We use information we collect to defend our legal rights, comply with state, local, federal or international laws, and to enforce our Terms of Service and this Notice.

**OUR DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE SERVICES**
----------------------------------------------------------------

There are certain circumstances in which we disclose information collected through the Services with certain other parties without further notice to you, as set forth below.

**A. Business Transfers:**As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, similar event, or steps taken in anticipation of such events (e.g., due diligence in a transaction), user information may be part of the transferred assets.  

**B. Affiliates and Subsidiaries**:  
We disclose your personal information among the GoFundMe entities, including our affiliates and subsidiaries, for purposes consistent with this Notice, such as to provide our Services including hosting; marketing and publicizing fundraisers; providing you with customer support; administering funds in connection with fundraisers; authenticating donors; sending you communications; improving services offered by the various GoFundMe entities and conducting the other activities described in this Notice.  

**C. Agents, Consultants, Vendors and Related Third Parties:  
**GoFundMe contracts with other companies to perform certain business-related functions on GoFundMe’s behalf, and we provide access to or disclose your information with these companies so they can perform services for us. Examples of such functions include marketing, mailing information, data storage, security, identity verification, fraud prevention, payment processing, legal services, and maintaining databases.  

**D. Unaffiliated Parties that Partner With Us or our Affiliate or Other Services You Choose to Link:  
**GoFundMe may disclose personal information to third parties that partner with us on various initiatives and/or that offer services you choose to link to your GoFundMe fundraiser or that are linked to a GoFundMe fundraiser to which you may donate.  Examples of this are Social Networking Services and their integrated social media tools or “plug-ins,” or other groups such as Caring Bridge or The Knot.  When you link to or interact directly with third-party companies (or you donate to GoFundMe fundraisers that are linked), their use of your personal information and your use of their features are governed by the privacy notices of those companies. We encourage you to carefully read their privacy notices.  

**E. Legal Requirements:  
**We may transfer, disclose and preserve your information to courts, law enforcement, governmental or public authorities, tax authorities, or authorized third parties, if and to the extent we are required or permitted to do so by law or where disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with our legal obligations, (ii) comply with a valid legal request (such as a subpoena or court order) or to respond to claims asserted against us, (iii) respond to a valid legal request relating to a criminal investigation to address alleged or suspected illegal activity, or to respond to or address any other activity that may expose us, you, or any other of our users or members of the public to imminent harm, legal or regulatory liability, (iv) enforce and administer our Terms of Service or other policies, or (v) protect the rights, property or personal safety of GoFundMe, its affiliates, its employees, its users, or members of the public.  

**F. Organizers and beneficiaries of fundraisers:  
**We may disclose your information with organizers and, if not the same, the beneficiaries of the fundraiser. For example, if you donate to a fundraiser for an individual, we disclose your name and donation information you have provided in connection with your donation with the organizer or beneficiary, who may contact you. If you selected to be “anonymous” on the public fundraiser pages on the Services, your name will still be visible to the organizer, any of their team members and the beneficiary and will be otherwise processed in accordance with this Privacy Notice. For example, if an individual starts a fundraiser for a Charity and you donate to that fundraiser, then if the information is requested, (i) the Charity can receive certain personal information about both the organizer, if not the same, and the donors, and (ii) organizer can receive donor information. In each case, GoFundMe would contractually require that  the beneficiary may only communicate with you about your donation and/or to comply with its legal and auditing requirements.  

**G. Your Consent  
**In certain situations, we may disclose your information in the event that you consent to the disclosure of your information. For example, we may partner with third party organizations to arrange for specific fundraisers. If you consent to our providing your contact information to a specific partner, we disclose, with the partner organization, your name, email address and other information you have provided in connection with your donation to the specific fundraiser.  

**H. Aggregated Data  
**We aggregate, anonymize and/or de-identify information collected actively or passively about you so that the information no longer relates to you individually.  We then use that data for various lawful purposes, including but not limited to our research on our customer demographics, interests and behavior. We also disclose this information with our affiliates, agents, business partners, research facilities or other third parties.  

**I. Cookies and Other Electronic Technologies  
**Information is disclosed as stated in the Section entitled “Cookies and Other Electronic Technologies.”  

**J. Other Users of Our Services  
**We provide your information to other users of our Services if you choose to make your information publicly available in a publicly accessible area of the Services, such as in your fundraiser or in the comments.

**VOLUNTEERED INFORMATION**
---------------------------

Please be advised that some information you provide may be publicly accessible, such as information posted in forums or comment sections. We also collect information through forums and communities, surveys and customer support communications, your communication to us of ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, feedback and other solicited or unsolicited submissions (collectively, with publicly-accessible information, “Volunteered Information”). By sending us Volunteered Information, you further  agree that we are under no obligation of confidentiality, express or implied, with respect to the Volunteered Information. This Volunteered Information section shall survive any termination of your account or the Services.

**CHILDREN**
------------

Our Services are not designed for use by individuals under the age of 13 (or 16 for children located in Europe). If you are under the age of 13 (or 16 for children located in Europe), please do not use the Services and/or submit any information through the Services. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 (or 16 for children located in Europe) has provided personal information to GoFundMe through the Services, please contact us at GFMlegal@gofundme.com, and we will delete that information from our databases to the extent required by law.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**
---------------------------

The Services can contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by GoFundMe (the “Third-Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third-Party Sites. The links from the Services do not imply that GoFundMe endorses or has reviewed the Third-Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their respective privacy policies.

**SECURITY**
------------

While no organization can guarantee perfect security, GoFundMe has implemented and seeks to continuously improve technical and organizational security measures to protect the information provided via the Services from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please see [here](https://www.gofundme.com/c/security) for details.  

**DO-NOT-TRACK SIGNALS**
------------------------

Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. We do not  respond to browser-initiated DNT signals. To learn more about Do Not Track, you can do so [here](http://allaboutdnt.com/). If you are a California consumer, you can view our “[California Privacy Notice](https://www.gofundme.com/c/ccpa)” to learn more about our recognition of other signals. 

**RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION**
---------------------------------

We retain your information for as long as we deem necessary for the purpose for which that information was collected and for our legitimate business operations; provided, however, that your information is only retained to the extent permitted or required by applicable laws. When we no longer need to retain your information, we will take reasonable steps to remove it from our systems and records and/or take steps to anonymize it so that you can no longer be identified from it in accordance with our internal document retention policies. When determining the retention period for your information, we take into account various criteria, such as the type of products and services requested by or provided to you, the nature and length of our relationship with you, possible re-enrolment with our products or services, the impact on the Services we provide to you if we delete some information about you, mandatory retention periods provided by law and the statute of limitations.

**CROSS BORDER DATA TRANSFERS**
-------------------------------

GoFundMe is a global organization headquartered in the United States, which processes your information in servers in a number of countries, including the United States. GoFundMe has implemented other appropriate cross-border transfer solutions, such as Standard Contractual Clauses approved by appropriate regulatory authorities, to provide adequate protection for transfers of certain personal data from the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, and Switzerland to the United States.

**USERS FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**
----------------------------------------

The Platform is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting the Platform from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located, and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, and data may be accessible to law enforcement and national security authorities under certain circumstances. 

**USERS IN EUROPE**
-------------------

If you are located in Europe, our legal grounds for processing your information may be as follows:

* Consent: Where you have given consent to such processing for one or more specific purposes.
* Contractual Obligation: Where the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you.
* Legal Obligation: Where processing is necessary for compliance with our legal obligation.
* Legitimate Interest: Where processing is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of our users and your interests and fundamental rights and freedoms do not override those interests.

We transfer your personal data to third countries subject to appropriate safeguards, such as standard contractual clauses.

If you are located in Europe, you have the right to ask for an overview of the information we process about you, and for a copy of your information. In addition, you may request us to update and correct inaccuracies, delete your information, restrict processing of your information, or exercise your right to data portability to easily transfer your information to another company. In some cases, you may object to the processing of your information and where we have asked you for your consent to process your information, you can withdraw it at any time. You may also withdraw a previously given consent for processing your personal information; the withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of the processing based on consent before its withdrawal. The above rights may be limited under applicable law.

You can make a request to exercise any of these rights in relation to your information by sending the request to us at the email address or mailing address set forth under [“Contacting GoFundMe.”](https://www.gofundme.com/c/privacy#contact) For your own privacy and security, at our discretion, we may require you to provide your identity before providing the requested information. Please note that GoFundMe may take up to 30 days after identity verification to fulfill such requests.

The above rights can be limited under applicable law. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the local data protection authority if you believe that we have not complied with applicable data protection laws. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority of your residence, place of work or where the incident took place.

The Irish Data Protection Commissioner shall act as the competent lead supervisory authority for users in the European Economic Area, and you have the right to lodge a compliant with your local data protection authority (see list in the l[ink https:](https://www.gofundme.com/blank)//ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index\_en.htm.)  The Information Commissioner’s Office shall act as the competent supervisory authority for users in the United Kingdom and the Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) for Switzerland.

**MARKETING OPT OUT**
---------------------

Each email marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt out” of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us at the email address or mailing address set forth under [“Contacting GoFundMe.”](https://www.gofundme.com/c/privacy#contact) If you opt out of receiving marketing communications or other information we think may interest you, we can still send you emails about your account or any Services you have requested or received from us.

**OTHER TERMS**
---------------

Your access to and use of the Services is subject to GoFundMe’s [Terms of Service](https://www.gofundme.com/c/terms) and such other terms, which may be made available to you in connection with your use of the Services.  

**CHANGES TO GOFUNDME’S PRIVACY NOTICE**
----------------------------------------

GoFundMe reserves the right to update or modify this Notice at any time and from time to time. We will notify you of any material updates or changes we make to this Notice. If you disagree with our revisions to the Notice, you can deactivate your account or discontinue the use of our Services. Please review this Notice periodically for any updates or changes to this Notice.

By using our Platform and Services after any such update or modification, you acknowledge that you have read and understood the terms of the Notice as updated or modified.

**CONTACTING GOFUNDME**
-----------------------

You can contact our Data Protection Officer by emailing [dpo@gofundme.com](mailto:dpo@gofundme.com). 

To submit a Data Subject Request, please fill out [this form](https://preferences.gofundme.com/privacy) or email [privacy-requests@gofundme.com](mailto:privacy-requests@gofundme.com). 

You can also contact us via mail as follows:

For users in the USA and the rest of the world (except Europe):

GoFundMe, Inc. and Classy Inc.  
℅ Legal Department  
PO Box 121270  
815 E Street  
San Diego, CA, 92101  
United States

For users in Europe:  
GoFundMe Ireland, Ltd.,  
℅ Legal Department  
70 Sir John Rogerson Quay,  
Dublin 2, Ireland.

Table of Contents

English (United States)English (Ireland)English (UK)English (Canada)Português (Portugal)Nederlands (Nederland)Italiano (Italia)Français (France)Español (España)Deutsch (Deutschland)

Fundraise for

Learn more

Resources

* More resources

More resources

© 2010-2024 GoFundMe [Terms](https://www.gofundme.com/c/terms) [Privacy](https://www.gofundme.com/c/privacy) [Legal](https://www.gofundme.com/legal) [Accessibility Statement](https://www.gofundme.com/c/accessibility-statement) [Your Privacy Choices ](https://www.gofundme.com/c/opt-out-rights)
